const questions = [
  {
    question: "which of the following is not an English team",
    options: ["Chelsea", "Man United", "Man City", "Barcelona"],
    answer: "Barcelona"
  },
  {
    question: "which team won the last champions league",
    options: ["Real Madrid", "Barcelona", "Liverpool", "Chelsea"],
    answer: "Liverpool"
  },
  {
    question: "Which country won the last world cup",
    options: ["France", "England", "Nigeria", "Spain"],
    answer: "France"
  },
  {
    question: "which of these players won the last fifa best player",
    options: ["L Messi", "C Ronaldo", "F Ribery", "E Hazard"],
    answer: "L Messi"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of this team is not a spanish team",
    options: ["Real Madrid", "Chelsea", "Barcelona", "Sevilla"],
    answer: "Chelsea"
  },
  {
    question: "Which country has won the world cup more",
    options: ["Germany", "France", "Brazil", "Spain"],
    answer: "Brazil"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is currently the coach of Chelsea Fc",
    options: ["F Lampard", "R Shina", "M Owen", "J Klop"],
    answer: "F Lampard"
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the last english premier league competition",
    options: ["Man United", "Chelsea", "Man City", "Liverpool"],
    answer: "Man City"
  },
  {
    question: "Ngolo Kante is a player at which of these Clubs",
    options: ["Liverpool", "Chelsea", "Man United", "Man city"],
    answer: "Chelsea"
  },
  {
    question: "M Salah is a player at which of these Clubs",
    options: ["Liverpool", "Chelsea", "Man United", "Man City"],
    answer: "Liverpool"
  }
];
